>> 布莱恩: 我们再去修另一个，让我们去修正细节吧， js 来了。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So let's go fix another one,
let's go fix details,js here.
所以我要去 details.js，我们想说重命名，想重命名
So I'm gonna go to details.js,
we wanna say rename, and we want to rename
这件事很明显它会对很多事情感到不安
this .tsx and obviously it's gonna
be upset about a great many things.
> > 布莱恩: 首先，它会被轮播和
&gt;&gt; Brian: So first of all,
it's gonna be upset by carousel and
错误边界，因为这些边界尚未输入。
error boundary because
those aren't typed yet.
我们以严格的方式
And we have it in strict mode,
这就意味着我们不接受任何 ANY ，对吧 ?
which basically means we
don't accept any ANYs, right?
任何一个都不知道是什么车
And ANY is like,
it doesn't know what carousel is.
就好像，我不知道这是什么，我很不高兴，对吧 ?
So it's just like, I don't know what
this is, and I'm upset about it, right?
所以它会以红色为基础
So it's gonna be underlying this in red,
这将会是一个错误，直到你去处理这个问题。
this is going to be an error until
you go type this one as well.
也许正确的事情是我们可能已经过去了
So probably correct order of things
is we probably could've gone and
先完成了轮播和错误的边界，但我们会得到它。
done carousel and error boundary first,
but we'll get to it.
所以现在让我们来处理这些错误。
So for now let's just deal
with these kinds of errors.
> > 布莱恩: 首先要知道的是， React，
&gt;&gt; Brian: So
the first thing to know is that, React,
你得告诉它它会得到什么样的道具
you have to tell it what kind of props
it's gonna get, for classes that is.
所以我们要给它一个类型的参数
So we're gonna give it
a type parameter here, and
我们会说这是 RouteComponentProps
we're gonna say that this
is a RouteComponentProps.
你可以看到它是什么样的，我想我知道那是什么，对吧 ?
And you can see there that it's like,
I think I know what that is, right?
所以如果我点击它会抓取到路由器的信息
So if I click that it's gonna
grab that from reach router.
> > 布莱恩:
&gt;&gt; Brian: And then this in of itself,
这些 RouteComponentProps 也接受另一个参数。
these RouteComponentProps
also takes another parameter.
这就像是函数调用中的函数调用
So it's like a function call
within a function call and
我们得告诉它你能期望得到什么样的东西
we have to tell it what kind of
things you can expect to get.
所以我们要告诉你我们要找个 id
So we're gonna tell that, hey,
we're expecting to get an id, and
那将会是一个弦
that's gonna be a string.
>> 布莱恩: 好的
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, so
现在知道 this.props.id 要么是字符串，要么是未定义的，对吗 ?
now it knows that this.props.id is either
gonna be a string or undefined, right?
因为如果他们到达细节路线
Because what happens if they
get to the details route
没找到 id 对吧
without getting an id, right?
因此，我们必须为此作出规定。
So we have to provide for that.
那么当我们到达 componentDidMount 并且没有字符串时会发生什么 ?
So what happens when we get to
componentDidMount and there's no string?
你在一个受伤的世界里
Well, you're in a world of hurt.
您需要一个标识，否则不应该在详细信息页面上。
You need an id or
you should not be on the details page.
我们告诉 RouteComponents ，对，
We tell that RouteComponents, right,
这将会得到一个 " id:string" 的参数。
that's going to get
a parameter of id:string.
现在基本上说我想你会得到一个 id
Now, it's basically gonna say,
I think you're gonna get an id, but
可能不合适吗
it might not come right?
这就是 id的意思吗
So that's what the id?
就好像我不知道它可能来了
is, like, I don't know, it might come.
所以，这意味着，如果不在那里，我们就必须提供结果。
So that means we have to provide for
what happens if it's not there.
那么，如果我们到达详细信息页面，并且没有提供任何标识，那么会发生什么情况 ?
So what happens if we get to the details
page and there was no id provided?
这就是你和我现在要决定的
That's what you and
I need to decide right now.
如果你上了这一页又没有 id 你不能留着
Well, if you get to this page and
there's no id, you can't stay on this
因为我不能给你看任何宠物给你看的宠物
page because I can't show you any pet if I
don't have any id for the pet to show you.
所以我们会说如果没有这方面的建议
So we're just gonna say if
there is no this.props.id,
你会说导航到 /
you're gonna say navigate to /, so
返回主页，然后返回。
go back to the homepage and then return.
这样就能照顾好一部分了
So that takes care of part of this.
现在我们知道我们到这里的时候了这肯定是在这里
So now we know by the time we get
down here, this is definitely here,
肯定会在那儿的
it's definitely gonna be there.
但问题是，动物期望什么 ?
But the problem is
pet.animal expects what?
这应该是个数字吧
It expects that to be a number, right?
所以让我们在这里做点魔法
So let's just do a little
of magic here and
说你现在是个数字 [ LAUGH] 是吧 ?
say well now you're
a number [LAUGH] right?
所以如果我把那个一元再加上
So if I put that unary plus there it's
会把这个从一个串里变成一个数字
gonna coerce that from
a string into a number.
好了现在它说好了我知道动物是什么
Okay and then now it says okay,
I know what an animal is and
有个动物有名字
an animal has a name.
这是一个字符串，它有一个类型。
And that's a string, and it has a type.
这是一个字符串，它有一个地址。
And that's a string,
and it has an address.
这是一个地址类型的对象。
And that's an object
that's an address type.
如果我点击这个，我可以去，好的，地址。
And if I click on that, I can go,
okay, well, address here.
然后这里有个地址是吧
And then it has an address here, right?
现在我只看类型的定义。
Now I'm just looking at
the type definition.
所以我可以看到一个组织是什么样的 ?
So I can see what does
an organization look like?
它总是有一个名字，但它有一封电子邮件，或者它没有，对吗 ?
It always has a name, but
it has an email or it doesn't, right?
这是我可以看到的非常好的文件。
So this is pretty good
documentation that I can look at.
太棒了因为我写的
It's fantastic because I wrote it.
开玩笑的我是说我确实写过但这不太妙
Just kidding, well I mean I did
write it but it's not fantastic.
我只是通过在这里做 Cmd + click 来设置。
And I just set up by doing Cmd
+ click on something here.
我就像 Cmd + click on contact，
Like I can just Cmd + click on contact,
and
它可以带我进入这个类型的定义来观察它的样子。
it can take me into the type
definition to see what that looks like.
或者你可以把它悬停在它上如果我写了 JS 文档
Or you can just hover on it,
and if I had written JS docs,
你也会在这里看到的对吧
you would've seen those here as well,
right?
如果我在这里看 " React.Component " ，那一个也没有。
Whereas if I look at React.Component here,
that one doesn't have it either.
其中一些文件也会有一些文件。
Some of these will have bits of
documentation with it as well.
比如你拍纪录片之类的东西
Like if you do documents.querySelector,
something like that,
，对，这些都有很好的记录。
right, these ones
are super well documented.
它会告诉您，返回作为节点后代的第一个元素
It will tell you, returns the first
element that is a descendant of the node
和选择器匹配对吧
that matches the selectors, right?
所以实际上它有直接的文档。
So it actually has inline documentation.
但这要求那个人不是懒惰的老师，
But that requires that the person
is not a lazy teacher, and
之前我没做过的
previously did that which I did not.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，这样就能处理好了。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, so
that takes care of this.
任何方式都能真正鼓励我们去做
One of the things that any modes going
to really, really encourage us to do
我们不需要，你可以看到这些是警告，而不是错误。
we don't have to, you can see that
these are warnings, not errors.
这是它想知道的，是这个公开的还是这个私人的 ?
Is that it wants to know is,
is this public or is this private?
嗯，反应成分中的所有东西都是通过反应来调用的。
Well, everything in react component
is being called by react.
所以技术上应该是公开的对吧
So it's technically gonna be public,
right?
所以我想说这是一个公共的国家，这是一个公共部门。
So I'm just gonna say this is a public
state and this is a public component.
ComponentDidMount ，即， right， cuz 反应正在调用这些内容。
ComponentDidMount that is, right,
cuz react is calling into these things.
但是如果我说了， >> 布莱恩: 私事，
But if I said like,
&gt;&gt; Brian: private thing = blah.
现在这是私有的， TypeScript 会捕捉到是否有人要打电话，
So now this is private, TypeScript will
catch if anyone else is trying to call,
就像不，不，不，那是私人的，你别碰那个，对吧 ?
it's like no, no, no, that's private,
you don't get to touch that, right?
但如果是公众的话其他事情就可以了
Whereas if it's public then it's okay for
other things to access it,
但现在 TypeScript 将是 enforcer 以确保这些东西是专用的。
but now TypeScript will be the enforcer
to make sure these things are private.
这也挺酷的
Which is pretty cool as well.
我们今天就不用这个了
We won't be using that today, but
我只是想把它叫做我喜欢的东西
I just wanted to call that out
as something that I liked.
> > 布莱恩: 好的， >> 布莱恩:
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay,
&gt;&gt; Brian: Everything else here,
它能找到相当好的轮廓
it's able to figure out pretty well.
我是说这不是真的
I mean, this, it doesn't really care for.
如果你愿意的话，你可以输入这个，说这会是一个错误。
If you want to, you can type this and
say this is gonna be an error.
你得把这些放在括号里
And you'll have to put
these in parentheses.
但现在明白了，这是个错误。
But now it knows like okay,
this is an error.
所以你可以在这里提供一些提示。
So you can give little hints here and
there.
所有这些我们都要公开
All of these, we're gonna say public.
>> Brian: this.state.url，它就像嘿，我不知道那是什么。
&gt;&gt; Brian: this.state.url, it's like hey,
I don't know what that is.
你能告诉我那是什么吗
So can you tell me what this.state.url is?
我也不知道这些是什么。
And it's like,
I don't know what these are either.
所以我们有两种方法可以解决这个国家未知的问题。
So there's two ways we can
handle this.state being unknown.
其中一个我们可以在这里
One of them, we could go up here and
我们可以在 RouteComponents 此处提供第二个参数。
we can give it a second parameter
after the RouteComponents here.
第一是道具，第二个是状态。
So the first one is props,
the second one is state.
或者在我看来，如果我们为所有这些都设定一个默认值，
Or in my opinion, better if we go set
a default value for all of these,
TypeScript 会按自己的值来处理所有内容，对吗 ?
TypeScript will figure everything
out just on its own, right?
所以如果我说我要去拿默认值
So if I say,
I'm just gonna go get a default value for
这个名字将会是 " 动物"
name, that's going to be "" animal, "",
位置， ""，描述， ""，介质。
location, "", description, "", media.
这会是个阵列
That's gonna be an array.
" " " 和 " " " 。
url is "" and breed is "".
> > 布莱恩: 所以现在知道了，如果我说你是个动物，
&gt;&gt; Brian: So now it knows okay,
if I say this.state.animal,
那将会是一个弦
that's gonna be a string.
是你告诉我的
You told me that.
>> Brian: 这仅适用于公共类属性。
&gt;&gt; Brian: This only works
with public class properties.
如果你在一个构造函数里面做这个，这不起作用。
If you're doing this inside of
a constructor, this doesn't work.
你得用其他的方法来说
You do have to actually use this
other method of saying, okay,
这会是这个什么的对吧
this is gonna be this and
that and whatever, right?
所以这里的 S 部分是你要给它的状态
So the S part of this is the state
that you're gonna give it.
> > 布莱恩: 但是因为我们有公共阶层的财产，
&gt;&gt; Brian: But
because we have public class properties,
它知道怎么理解这个
it knows how to understand this.
所以我们还有一个问题。
So we have one more problem.
所以注意这些东西现在都很好了
So notice that all this stuff is fine now.
也许我们还有一个问题
We have one more problem, probably.
>> Brian: 请注意，此介质上的类型永远不存在。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Notice that the type
here on this media is a never.
这不是件好事对吧
That's not a good thing, right?
这就意味着，你告诉我这是一个数组，但是
This basically means like, all right
you told me this is an array, but
你没告诉我是什么样的阵列，所以我让你有一个阵列，但是
you didn't tell me what kind of array it
is, so I'll let you have an array, but
不碰它， [LAUGH] 对吧 ?
never touch it, [LAUGH] right?
这就是它跟你说的
That's kind of what it's telling you here.
所以我们得告诉它会有什么样的东西
So we have to tell it what kind
of stuff is gonna go into it.
我来教你怎么做
So I'll show you how to do that.
你要过来跟媒体说你是照片 [ ]
You're gonna come up here to media and
you're gonna say as Photo[ ].
照片要从前面的主人/宠物那里来。
And so Photo is going to come from
frontendmasters/pet right here.
这将是一个照片。
So this is gonna be a Photo.
>> Brian: 现在， >> Brian: 如果我在这里
&gt;&gt; Brian: Now,
&gt;&gt; Brian: If I go down here and
看看媒体，无论去哪里，媒体。
look at media, wherever that went, media.
> > 布莱恩: 会说好的，很酷，你现在可以用了。
&gt;&gt; Brian: It's gonna say okay,
cool, you can use that now.
>> 演讲者 2: 例如，您是否可以使用诸如视频之类的多个媒体类型 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Can you use multiple
media types like video, for example?
> > 布莱恩: 你肯定能
&gt;&gt; Brian: You definitely could, and
那你就会有所谓的工会式了吧
then you would have what's
called a union type, right?
那么如果是视频类型，那么您就必须显示 TypeScript ，
So then you would have to show
TypeScript if this is of type video,
那么它就有这种东西，对吧 ?
then it has these kind of things, right?
你必须做一些所谓的改进来了解你的
And you have to do some what's called type
refinement to figure out which kind your
处理，但是可以混合，对。
dealing with, but it can be mixed, right.
我不知道我今天是否要向你展示
I don't know if I'm gonna show
you anything like that today, but
只要查一查就好了你就知道了
just look up type refinement,
and you'll see.
> > 布莱恩: 酷，那是个好问题。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Cool, that was a good question.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，在下面，我们会说，这不是我不知道的
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, down here, we're gonna
say, it's not like I don't know what these
道具是我很不自在
props are and
I'm uncomfortable about that.
所以我们首先要告诉它的是
So the first thing we're
gonna tell it here is,
> > 布莱恩: 这些道具
&gt;&gt; Brian: These props are gonna be exactly
就像在这里一样
the same as these ones up here.
因此，您实际上可以只复制+粘贴这些内容。
So you can actually just
Copy+Paste these ones.
在其中包含字符串的 routeComponents 。
The routeComponents with
the string in there.
我们会把它变成那样的
And we're just going to pass
that into that, like that.
> > 布莱恩: 然后一切都很开心
&gt;&gt; Brian: And then everything is happy.
> > 布莱恩: 我想现在唯一不高兴的是这两个
&gt;&gt; Brian: And I think the only thing that
it's upset about right now is these two
从顶部进口，对吗 ?
imports at the top, right?
你可以看到我有红色的感觉就像
So you can see there I have red
right there, and it's like,
这个文件有问题对吧
hey there's problems with this file,
right?
但现在我无法解决这些问题，直到我去修复这些其他文件。
But for now I can't fix these until
I go and fix these other files.
但是如果我把严格的方式关掉，那就好了。
But so if I turn strict mode off of here,
then it would be fine.